×  

### Python

### AI, ML and Data Science

### Java

### B.Tech and MCA

### Web Technology

### Software Testing

×  

### Technical Interview

### Java Interview

### Web Interview

### Database Interview

### Company Interviews

Privacy
-------

Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address or other details to help you with your experience.

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on our site.

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

* To improve our website in order to better serve you.
* To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

### How do we protect visitor information?

We do not use an SSL certificate

* We only provide articles and information, and we never ask for personal or private information

### No Refund and No Cancellation Policy

There is no refund and no cancellation policy for training, development and seo services.

### Do we use 'cookies'?

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

### Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

### Third party links

We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.

**Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

**We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**

* Google Display Network Impression Reporting
* Demographics and Interests Reporting

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out:

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

### Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via email

* Within 1 business day

We will notify the users via in site notification

* Within 1 business day

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**

* Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**To be accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:**

* NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
* Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
* Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can

* Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may Contact Us.

Learn Important Tutorial
------------------------

[

Python](https://www.javatpoint.com/python-tutorial)

[

Java](https://www.javatpoint.com/java-tutorial)

[

Javascript](https://www.javatpoint.com/javascript-tutorial)

[

HTML](https://www.javatpoint.com/html-tutorial)

[

Database](https://www.javatpoint.com/sql-create-database)

[

PHP](https://www.javatpoint.com/php-tutorial)

[

C++](https://www.javatpoint.com/cpp-tutorial)

[

React](https://www.javatpoint.com/reactjs-tutorial)

B.Tech / MCA
------------

[

DBMS](https://www.javatpoint.com/dbms-tutorial)

[

Data Structures](https://www.javatpoint.com/data-structure-tutorial)

[

DAA](https://www.javatpoint.com/daa-tutorial)

[

Operating System](https://www.javatpoint.com/operating-system)

[

Computer Network](https://www.javatpoint.com/computer-network-tutorial)

[

Compiler Design](https://www.javatpoint.com/compiler-tutorial)

[

Computer Organization](https://www.javatpoint.com/computer-organization-and-architecture-tutorial)

[

Discrete Mathematics](https://www.javatpoint.com/discrete-mathematics-tutorial)

[

Ethical Hacking](https://www.javatpoint.com/ethical-hacking)

[

Computer Graphics](https://www.javatpoint.com/computer-graphics-tutorial)

[

Web Technology](https://www.javatpoint.com/html-tutorial)

[

Software Engineering](https://www.javatpoint.com/software-engineering)

[

Cyber Security](https://www.javatpoint.com/cyber-security-tutorial)

[

Automata](https://www.javatpoint.com/automata-tutorial)

[

C Programming](https://www.javatpoint.com/c-programming-language-tutorial)

[

C++](https://www.javatpoint.com/cpp-tutorial)

[

Java](https://www.javatpoint.com/java-tutorial)

[

.Net](https://www.javatpoint.com/net-framework)

[

Python](https://www.javatpoint.com/python-tutorial)

[

Programs](https://www.javatpoint.com/programs-list)

[

Control System](https://www.javatpoint.com/control-system-tutorial)

[

Data Warehouse](https://www.javatpoint.com/data-warehouse)

Preparation
-----------

[

Aptitude](https://www.javatpoint.com/aptitude/quantitative)

[

Reasoning](https://www.javatpoint.com/reasoning)

[

Verbal Ability](https://www.javatpoint.com/verbal-ability)

[

Interview Questions](https://www.javatpoint.com/interview-questions-and-answers)

[

Company Questions](https://www.javatpoint.com/company-interview-questions-and-recruitment-process)

We provides tutorials and interview questions of all technology like java tutorial, android, java frameworks

##### Contact info

G-13, 2nd Floor, Sec-3, Noida, UP, 201301, India

[\[email protected\]](https://www.javatpoint.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

##### Follow us

##### Tutorials

##### Interview Questions

##### Online Compiler

© Copyright 2024 Javatpoint. All Rights Reserved.
